Lavanya Maganti

lavv89@gmail.com (812)262-8457

Career Objective

To excel in my field of expertise there by providing the best of my efforts in to the professionally managed organization, this allows me to expand upon m knowledge and skills by contributing in the best way to perform extra ordinarily well.

Education

Indiana State University Terre Haute, IN **Masters in Computer Science** Expected Dec 2017

GPA: 4.0/4.0

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University Hyderabad, India May 2014

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering

GPA: 3.5/4.0

Work Experience

Wells Fargo India Solutions, Hyderabad, India

Sep 2014 - Jan 2016

Assistant Software Engineer

- Worked as an Assistant Software Engineer under Production Readiness and Environment Support
- Involved in implementation of builds, reviewing and scheduling of jobs in production and nonproduction environments using Autosys tool.
- Triage issues and tickets, facilitate root-cause determination thus, manage problem life cycle to completion.
- Maintained database by validating and testing the accuracy of populated data.
- Creating logon manager connections, global variables which are required for autosys jobs to run successfully.

Ozonotel PVT LTD, India

Jun 2013 - Aug 2014

PHP/Web developer

- Worked as a PHP/Web developer under Developer team.
- Involved in developing PHP telephonic applications and web applications as per client requirement.
- Web development programming in client/server side.

Relevant Work Experience

Indiana State University, Terre Haute IN

Aug 2016 – Dec 2016

Graduate Assistant

- Worked as an Administrative intern in Math and Computer Science Department.
- Unix/Linux lab assistant.

Indiana State University, Terre Haute IN

Jan 2017 - Present

Graduate Assistant/Teaching Assistant

- Working as an instructor for CS151 course (Introduction to Computer Science) which covers HTML/CSS and Java Scripting.
- Unix/Linux lab assistant.

Projects:

Student Information System: (Environment: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, My SQL, PHP, Sqlite3)

• A Database project which helps the user to enter new student details and which intern will upload/store the information into the database.

Flexi Editor: (Environment: Visual Studio 2008, C# .NET, ASP.NET)

• An enriched text editor with advanced features.

Periodicity Detection in Data Mining: (Environment: Java, Netbeans)

 Mine (extract useful data) data from large volume of data database based on their periodicity value.

Leadershipp & Volunteer Work:

- Coordinated "AURA2K12" a national level Techno-Cultural Fest conducted in march 2012
- Volunteered 1st IEEE POWER COLLOQUIUM organized by IEEE ATRI Student Branch And IEEE PES/IAS/PELS joint chapter ,Hyderabad Section in March 2012
- Volunteered 2nd IEEE Computing Colloquium conducted in July 2011.
- Present member of **Indian Student Association** which is part of **ISU**(Indiana State University).
- Member of **ACM student club**, ISU(Indiana State University).

Skills:

Programming	Web Technologies	Databases	Tools
Languages	HTML, HTML 5, PHP, CSS,	MySQL, SQ LITE3	Word press, Autosys,
C , C++, JAVA, SHELL	JAVA SCRIPT, XML		Anthil, Harweb, SCM
SCRIPTS, LINUX			
Operating Systems	Others	Software's	IDE
Windows, Linux, Unix,	Apache Tomcat,	FTP, Win SCP, Ms-Office,	Net beans, Eclipse,
Android	Bootstrap	Putty	Microsoft Visual Studio